

# LISANDRO BIGI

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

### **PROFILE**

Hello! My name is Lisandro Bigi. I'm from Córdoba, Argentina, and I'm a Front End Developer (Full Stack in training) and an Anthropologist. I'm enthusiastic about technology and I have an advanced English level. I have knowledge in: HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | Git | Bootstrap | Sass | Node.js | Vue.js | React | Angular. I'm interested in Web Development, Responsive or Adaptive Web Design, User Interfaces (UI), User Experience (UX), Front-end and Web Design.

## CONTACT

351 631 9690

bigilisandro@gmail.com

Córdoba, Argentina

## SKILLS

HTML	• • • •
CSS	• • • •
JavaScript	• • • •
Vue.js	• • • •
React	• • • •
English	• • • •
Git	

## **EDUCATION**

**ACAMICA**, Full Stack Web Development

NOVEMBER 2019 - JUNE 2020

It is a seven-month duration course and includes the completion of three projects. Technologies applied: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL, among others.

**CODERHOUSE**, UX/UI Design

MAY 2020 - PRESENT

Twelve-week course in which I will learn about all the edges of User Experience in digital products.

FFyH - UNC, Anthropology Degree

FEBRAURY 2013 - MARCH 2020

Graduate in Anthropology (Faculty of Philosophy and Humanities - National University of Córdoba). Final average: 8.6

**CODERHOUSE**, Web Designer

OCTUBRE 2019 - DICIEMBRE 2019

Nine-week course where I learned how to create websites from a paper prototype using mainly HTML and CSS.

## EXPERIENCE

### **PENGYI LABS**, Front-end developer

JUNE 2020 - PRESENT

Currently working as a Front-end developer for a software company of Costa Rica with projects in Vue and React for clients all around the world.

**KICKSTA**, Front-end developer

OCTOBER 2020 - NOVEMBER 2021

I worked for this US company in their own main product Kicksta and in their others web applications such as InfluenceGrid and Wedding Hashers.



